Finding Aid for Detroit News records.
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Visual Materials
  - Negatives
    - Glass Plate Negatives
      - Mailing Room-Old Building, undated
      - New Building-Exterior-Detail of Main Entrance-Best, undated
      - New Building-Exterior-from 2nd floor American Boy Building, Trees Break 2nd Ave Side, undated
      - New Building-Exterior-Front Elevation-Does Not Show Shipping Room Entrance-Inferior Negative, undated
      - New Building-Exterior-News Building and Storage Warehouse-Showing "News" Building Proper in Foreground, undated
      - New Building-Exterior-Winter View, Light Snow-From American Boy Entrance, undated
      - New Building-Interior-Art Department-Artists' Desks from Gallery to Clock, undated
      - New Building-Interior-Art Department-Director's Desk to Photo Gallery-Drawing Boards Slightly out of Line, undated
      - New Building-Interior-Art Department-From Director's Desk to Photograph Gallery, undated
      - New Building-Interior-Art Department-Photo Gallery, undated
      - New Building-Interior-Art Department-Photo Gallery, undated
      - New Building-Interior-Art Department Positive Transparency of Photo Gallery, undated
      - New Building-Interior-Barber Shop, undated
      - New Building-Interior-Mr. Booth's Office-Mr. Booth's Desk, undated
      - New Building-Interior-Mr. Booth's Office-Close-up of Fireplace Showing Detail of Woodcarving over Mantel, undated
      - New Building-Interior-Mr. Booth's Office-Fireplace View-Best Negative, undated
      - New Building-Interior-Mr. Booth's Office-Fireplace View-Chair Conceals Humidor-Secondary Negative, undated
      - New Building-Interior-Mr. Booth's Office-Reception Room, undated
      - New Building-Interior-Business Offices-Advertising-Best Picture, undated
      - New Building-Interior-Business Offices-Circulation Department from Manager's Desk, undated
      - New Building-Interior-Business Offices-Detail of Main Entrance Looking into Lobby, undated
      - New Building-Interior-Business Offices-Looking Down Lobby from Entrance, undated
      - New Building-Interior-Café, undated
      - New Building-Interior-Café, undated
      - New Building-Interior-Café-Positive, undated
      - New Building-Interior-Composing Room-Fragmentary View Showing Proof Readers, undated
      - New Building-Interior-Composing Room-Positive, undated
      - New Building-Interior-Composing Room-Wide Angle (Best Picture)-8 x 11 Negative, undated
      - New Building-Interior-Conference Room-8 x 11 Reduction, undated
      - New Building-Interior-Conference Room-Positive Transparency, undated
      - New Building-Interior-Editorial Department-8 x 11 Reduction of Best Picture of News Room, undated
      - New Building-Interior-Editorial Department-8 x 11 Reduction of Best Picture of News Room, undated
      - New Building-Interior-Editorial Department-Exchanges, undated
      - New Building-Interior-Editorial Department-News Room-Best Negative, undated
      - New Building-Interior-Editorial Department-News Room-Inferior Negative (One of Two Taken), undated
      - New Building-Interior-Editorial Department-News Room-Positive, undated
      - New Building-Interior-Editorial Department-Society and Music, undated
      - New Building-Interior-Editorial Department-Society and Music-8 x11 Reduction, undated
      - New Building-Interior-Editorial Department-Special Writers' Room-Best Picture, undated
      - New Building-Interior-Editorial Department-Special Writers' Room-Showing Bookcases-Second Quality, undated
      - New Building-Interior-Editorial Society-Positive, undated
      - New Building-Interior-Editor's Office-Vertical Looking into Scripps' Office-Edge Chipped; Nearly Duplicates Other, undated
      - New Building-Interior-Engraving Department, undated
      - New Building-Interior-Engraving Department, undated
      - New Building-Interior-Engraving Department-Positive, undated
      - New Building-Interior-Files-Bound Volumes of News with Catlin, undated
      - New Building-Interior-Hospital-8x11 reduction, undated
      - New Building-Interior-Hospital-Positive, undated
      - New Building-Interior-Hospital-With Nurse in Attendance, undated
      - New Building-Interior-Lavatory-Composing Room Lavatory-Wash Room, undated
      - New Building-Interior-Library-Joined Negative-Panoramic Effect-Best picture, undated
      - New Building-Interior-Library-One section, East stacks only-Not a full view, undated
      - New Building-Interior-Library-One section, west stacks only-Not a full view, undated
      - New Building-Interior-Library-Positive, undated
      - New Building-Interior-Lockers-Composing Room Locker Room (vertical), undated
      - New Building-Interior-Machine Shop-Basement, undated
      - New Building-Interior-Mezzanine Corridor, Looking into President's suite, undated
      - New Building-Interior-Office of Secretary to Editor-in-Chief-3rd Floor, undated
      - New Building-Interior-Paper Storage-Positive, undated
      - New Building-Interior-Pent House-Freight Elevator Hoist Conspicuous, undated
      - New Building-Interior-Pent House-North Elevator Hoist, undated
      - New Building-Interior-Pent House-Tanks, Refrigeration and Washed Air Equipment, undated
      - New Building-Interior-Press and Mailing Room-Positive, undated
      - New Building-Interior-Press Control-Transparency, undated
      - New Building-Interior-Press Control Board-8x11 Reduction, undated
      - New Building-Interior-Press Paper Reels 8x11 Reduction, undated
      - New Building-Interior-Press Reels-Positive, undated
      - New Building-Interior-Press Room-Bird's eye view looking into the mailing room, undated
      - New Building-Interior-Press Room-Color Press, undated
      - New Building-Interior-Press Room from balcony-8x11 Reduction Mailing Room in Action, undated
      - New Building-Interior-Press Room Ground view from Northeast corner, undated
      - New Building-Interior-Press Room Ground view from Northeast corner, undated
      - New Building-Interior-Press Room Ground view from Northeast corner-8x11 Reduction, undated
      - New Building-Interior-Press Room-Paper storage-8x11 Reduction, undated
      - New Building-Interior-Presses-Transparency-Positive, undated
      - New Building-Interior-Receiving and Supplies-Job printing equipment, undated
      - New Building-Interior-Receiving and Supplies-Showing shelving and stock, undated
      - New Building-Interior-Reception Room on Mezzanine, undated
      - New Building-Interior-Reference Department, undated
      - New Building-Interior-Roto Camera, undated
      - New Building-Interior-Scott's Office 8x11 Reduction, undated
      - New Building-Interior-Scott's Office-Door to Scripps' Office closed, showing detail of woodcarving, undated
      - New Building-Interior-Scott's Office-Positive, undated
      - New Building-Interior-Shipping Room-Long view with cars parked, undated
      - New Building-Interior-Shipping Room-Positive, undated
      - New Building-Interior-Shipping Room-Unloading rolls and loading paper 8x11 Reduction, undated
      - New Building-Interior-Society Department, undated
      - New Building-Interior-Stereotypers-Positive, undated
      - New Building-Interior-Stereotypes in Action-8 x 11 Reduction, undated
      - New Building-Interior-Stereotyping Department-Natural Action-Men at work-Best Negative, undated
      - New Building-Interior-Stereotyping Department-with full staff posing for portraits, undated
      - New Building-Interior-Sub-Station-Edison Company Installation, undated
      - New Building-Interior-Telegraph 8x11 Reduction, undated
      - New Building-Interior-Telegraph Room-Positive, undated
      - New Building-Interior-Veterans of the News Staff-Men with news in 1890 still here in 1918 ca. 1918
      - New Building-Interior-Windows, undated, 2 negatives
      - New Building-Interior-Windows, undated, 2 negatives
      - Paper Hoist, undated
      - Paper Hoist, undated
      - Paper Rolls-Horse Drawn, undated
      - Paper Rolls-Horse Drawn, undated
      - Paper Warehouse, undated
      - Photo Department, undated
      - Photo Department-Chemical Room, undated
      - Photo Department-Studio, undated
      - Press Room, undated
      - Press Room, undated
      - Press Room, undated
      - Press Room, undated
      - Press Room, undated
      - Press Room, undated
      - Press Room, undated
      - Press Room, undated
      - Press Room, undated
      - Press Room-Paper Reels, undated
      - Radio-Lathrop at Desk, undated
      - Radio-Mandolin Club, undated
      - Radio-Office, undated
      - Radio-Quartet, undated
      - Radio-Shop, undated
      - Radio-University of Michigan Glee Club, undated
      - Radio-Yost, undated
      - Roto, undated, 2 negatives
      - Roto Etching, undated
      - Roto Plating and Grinding, undated
      - Roto Press, undated
      - Roto Press Room, undated
      - Scraparium, undated
      - Stereotype, 1912
      - Stereotype, ca. 1912
      - Stereotype, undated
      - Switchboard, undated
  - Photographic Prints
    The Photographic Print subseries (circa 1917- circa 1930s, 0.25 linear feet) contains photographic prints depicting the Detroit News building. All photographic prints are 11 x 14 inches in size. Prints were originally received in the same folder with corresponding glass plate negatives but have been removed and stored separately for preservation purposes. See the container list of this finding aid for corresponding materials.
    - Art Department-Kraemer's Corner, undated (Box 24)
    - Automatic Telephone, undated (Box 24)
    - Bindery, undated (2 prints) (Box 24)
    - Bingay's Office, undated (Box 24)
    - Building Exterior, undated (Box 24)
    - Critics, undated (Box 24)
    - Exterior-from 2nd floor American Boy Building, Trees Break 2nd Ave Side, undated (2 prints) (Box 24)
    - Garage Repair Shop, undated (Box 24)
    - Ink Tanks, undated (Box 24)
    - Lobby-3rd Floor-New Building, circa 1917 (Box 24)
    - New Building-Interior-Office of Secretary to Editor-in-Chief-3rd Floor, undated (Box 24)
    - New Building-Interior-Reception Room on Mezzanine, undated (Box 24)
    - New Building-Interior-Reference Department, undated (Box 24)
    - New Building-Interior-Society Department, undated (Box 24)
    - Paper Hoist, undated (Box 24)
    - Paper Hoist, undated (Box 24)
    - Press Room-Paper Reels, undated (Box 24)
    - Radio-Mandolin Club, undated (Box 24)
    - Radio-Shop, undated (Box 24)
    - Radio-Yost, undated (Box 24)
    - Roto Plating and Grinding, undated (Box 24)
    - Roto Press, undated (Box 24)
    - Scraparium, undated (Box 24)
    - Switchboard, undated (Box 24)
- Scrapbooks
  The Scrapbooks series (1856-1991, 154.5 linear feet in 156 boxes) includes books containing newspaper clippings that were collected and maintained by employees of the Detroit News. These scrapbooks are arranged alphabetically by subject. Subjects include local Detroit politicians, George G. Milliken, George Romney, and G. Mennen Williams and other public figures, such as Joe Louis and Ty Cobb. Various corporations are also represented, including Ford Motor Company and Michigan Bell Telephone Company. In addition to public figures and corporations, subjects range from Michigan legislature and election results to the race riots in Detroit. The contents within each book include article clippings arranged alphabetically by topic and each topic is arranged in loosely chronological order. Subjects often span multiple scrapbooks and boxes as detailed in the container list of this finding aid. Researchers interested in local Detroit news as well as regional, national, and global news as covered by the Detroit News may find these materials valuable. Scrapbooks pertaining to Eleanor Roosevelt can be found in the container list under, Mrs. Franklin D. Roosevelt, as she is referred to by the newspaper.
  - Agnew, Spiro T.-Politician-Book 1 A-G, 1968-1982 (Box 25)
  - Agnew, Spiro T.-Politician-Scrapbook Pages, 1983 (Box 25)
  - Agnew, Spiro T.-Politician-Book 2 H-R, 1967-1976 (Box 25)
  - Agnew, Spiro T.-Politician-Book 3 S-U, 1968-1975 (Box 25)
  - Agnew, Spiro T.-Politician-Book 4 V-Y, 1968-1982 (Box 25)
  - Alger Jr., Fred M. 1925-1967 (Box 25)
  - Ali, Muhammad-Boxer-Book 1 A-F, 1963-1981 (Box 25)
  - Ali, Muhammad-Boxer Book 2 F-Z and Miscellaneous, 1961-1980 (Box 26)
  - Ali, Muhammad-Boxer Book 3 Miscellaneous 1966-1982 (Box 26)
  - Americans in Iran-Book 1, 1976-1981 (Box 26)
  - Americans in Iran-Book 2 Miscellaneous January 1-May 1, 1980 (Box 26)
  - Americans in Iran-Book 3 Miscellaneous May 2-December 31, 1980 (Box 26)
  - Americans in Iran-Book 4 Miscellaneous 1981-1982 (Box 26)
  - Americans in Iran-Folder Miscellaneous 1983-1984 (Box 26)
  - Americans in Vietnam, 1983-1984 (Box 27)
  - Americans in Vietnam, 1963-1981 (Box 27)
  - American Motors Corporation-Employees-Collective Bargaining 1954-1982 (Box 27)
  - American Motors Corporation-Employees-Collective Bargaining (Box 27)
  - Anderson, John B. 1968-1981 (Box 27)
  - Auto Industry-Book 1 A-C, 1930-1982 (Box 27)
  - Auto Industry-Book 2 C-D, 1921-1982 (Box 27)
  - Auto Industry-Book 3 E, 1926-1982 (Box 28)
  - Auto Industry-Book 4 E-I, 1921-1982 (Box 28)
  - Auto Industry-Book 5 J-T, 1934-1982 (Box 28)
  - Auto Industry-Book 6 U-Z and Miscellaneous, 1918-1982 (Box 28)
  - Automobiles-Models-Series, 1974-1980 (Box 29)
  - Automobiles-Models-Series, 1983-1984 (Box 29)
  - Automobiles-Races -- Indianapolis, Book 1 A-Z and Miscellaneous, 1920-1970 (Box 29)
  - Automobiles-Races-Indianapolis Book 2 Miscellaneous 1955-1970 (Box 29)
  - Automobiles-Races-Indianapolis Book 3, 1971-1982 (Box 29)
  - Bagwell, Paul D.-Politician, 1958-1973 (Box 30)
  - Baseball-Games-All-Star-Book 1 A-Z, 1933-1963 (Box 30)
  - Baseball-Games-All-Star-Book 2, 1964-1982 (Box 30)
  - Baseball-World Series-Book 1, 1925-1956 (Box 30)
  - Baseball-World Series-Book 1A, 1921-1938 (Box 30)
  - Baseball-World Series-Book 2, 1939-1944 (Box 30)
  - Baseball-World Series-Book 3, 1945-1949 (Box 31)
  - Baseball-World Series-Book 4, 1950-1960 (Box 31)
  - Baseball-World Series-Book 5, 1961-1967 (Box 31)
  - Baseball-World Series-Book 6, 1968-1972 (Box 31)
  - Baseball-World Series-Book 7, 1973-1982 (Box 31)
  - Beck, Mary V.-Politician, 1946-1969 (Box 31)
  - Bentley, Alvin-Politician-Book 1 A-Z and Miscellaneous, 1952-1971 (Box 32)
  - Bowles, Charles-Detroit Mayor-Book 1, 1924-1950 (Box 32)
  - Bowles, Charles-Detroit Mayor-Book 2, 1924-1929 (Box 32)
  - Bowles, Charles-Detroit Mayor-Book 3, 1930 (Box 32)
  - Bowles, Charles-Detroit Mayor-Book 4, 1929-1957 (Box 32)
  - Bridges-Ambassador-Book 1, 1919-1982 (Box 32)
  - Brown, Prentiss M.-Politician, 1934-1977 (Box 33)
  - Brucker, Wilber M.-Governor-Book 1 A-G, 1921-1964 (Box 33)
  - Brucker, Wilber M.-Governor-Book 2 H-Z and Miscellaneous, 1930-1977 (Box 33)
  - Buckley, Gerald-Radio Commentator Murdered, 1930-1931 (Box 33)
  - Buckley, Gerald-Radio Commentator Murdered, 1931-1968 (Box 33)
  - Carter, Jimmy President-Book 1 A, 1976-1981 (Box 34)
  - Carter, Jimmy President-Book 2 A, 1976-1981 (Box 34)
  - Carter, Jimmy President-Book 3 B, 1971-1981 (Box 34)
  - Carter, Jimmy President-Book 4 C, 1976-1980 (Box 34)
  - Carter, Jimmy President-Book 5 C-D, 1976-1981 (Box 35)
  - Carter, Jimmy President-Book 6 E, 1976-1980 (Box 35)
  - Carter, Jimmy President-Book 7 E, 1976-1982 (Box 35)
  - Carter, Jimmy President-Book 8 G-H, 1970-1981 (Box 35)
  - Carter, Jimmy President-Book 9 I, 1976-1980 (Box 36)
  - Carter, Jimmy President-Book 10 I-K, 1976-1981 (Box 36)
  - Carter, Jimmy President-Book 11 L-M, 1976-1981 (Box 36)
  - Carter, Jimmy President-Book 12 M, 1976-1980 (Box 36)
  - Carter, Jimmy President-Book 13 N, 1976-1980 (Box 36)
  - Carter, Jimmy President-Book 14 N-O, 1976-1980 (Box 37)
  - Carter, Jimmy President-Book 15 O-P, 1976-1980 (Box 37)
  - Carter, Jimmy President-Book 16 P, 1976-1981 (Box 37)
  - Carter, Jimmy President-Book 17 P, 1976-1980 (Box 37)
  - Carter, Jimmy President-Book 18 P, 1975-1981 (Box 38)
  - Carter, Jimmy President-Book 19 P-R, 1976-1982 (Box 38)
  - Carter, Jimmy President-Book 20 S, 1976-1982 (Box 38)
  - Carter, Jimmy President-Book 21 S-T, 1976-1980 (Box 38)
  - Carter, Jimmy President-Book 22 T-V, 1976-1981 (Box 38)
  - Carter, Jimmy President-Book 23 V-Z and Miscellaneous, 1976-1981 (Box 39)
  - Castro, Fidel Cuban Leader-Book 1 A-R, 1959-1982 (Box 39)
  - Castro, Fidel Cuban Leader-Book 2 R-Z and Miscellaneous, 1958-1982 (Box 39)
  - Cavanagh, Jerome P.-Politician-Book 1 A-B, 1961-1982 (Box 39)
  - Cavanagh, Jerome P.-Politician-Book 2 C-D, 1961-1979 (Box 39)
  - Cavanagh, Jerome P.-Politician-Book 3 E-K, 1961-1974 (Box 40)
  - Cavanagh, Jerome P.-Politician-Book 4 L-N, 1961-1981 (Box 40)
  - Cavanagh, Jerome P.-Politician-Book 5 O-R, 1961-1974 (Box 40)
  - Cavanagh, Jerome P.-Politician-Book 6 S, 1961-1978
    - Cavanagh, Jerome P.-Politician-Book 7 T-Z and Miscellaneous, 1958-1979 (Box 40)
  - Chrysler Corporation-Employees-Collective Bargaining-UAW-Book 1, 1937-1961 (Box 41)
  - Chrysler Corporation-Employees-Collective Bargaining-UAW-Book 2, 1962-1978 (Box 41)
  - Chrysler Corporation-Employees-Collective Bargaining-Book 3, 1937-1982 (Box 41)
  - Chrysler Corporation-Employees-Strikes-Book 1, 1937-1958 (Box 41)
  - Chrysler Corporation-Employees-Strikes-Book 2, 1950-1982 (Box 41)
  - Churchill, Winston-British Statesman-Book 1 A-G, 1940-1982 (Box 42)
  - Churchill, Winston-British Statesman-Book 2 H-R, 1931-1981 (Box 42)
  - Churchill, Winston-British Statesman-Book 3 S-T, 1929-1961 (Box 42)
  - Churchill, Winston-British Statesman-Book 4 U-Z and Miscellaneous, 1924-1976 (Box 42)
  - Cobb, Tyrus-Baseball, 1914-1982 (Box 42)
  - Cobb, Tyrus-Baseball Biographical-Series by H. G. Salsinger, 1924 (Box 42)
  - Cobo, Albert E.-Mayor of Detroit-Book 1 A-E, 1933-1970 (Box 43)
  - Cobo, Albert E.-Mayor of Detroit-Book 2 F-L, 1938-1979 (Box 43)
  - Cobo, Albert E.-Mayor of Detroit-Book 3 M-R, 1936-1967 (Box 43)
  - Cobo, Albert E.-Mayor of Detroit-Book 4 S-Z and Miscellaneous, 1934-1957 (Box 43)
  - Colleges-Detroit, University of-Football-Games, 1922-1970 (Box 43)
  - Colleges-Michigan, University of-Football-Games-Book 1 A-L, 1918-1982 (Box 43)
  - Colleges-Michigan, University of-Football-Games-Book 2 M-N, 1923-1982 (Box 44)
  - Colleges-Michigan, University of-Football-Games-Book 3 N-P, 1918-1982 (Box 44)
  - Colleges-Michigan, University of-Football-Games-Book 4 Q-Z and Miscellaneous, 1921-1982 (Box 44)
  - Colleges-Michigan State-Football-Games-Book 1 A-M, 1929-1981 (Box 44)
  - Colleges-Michigan State-Football-Games-Book 2 M-O, 1936-1981 (Box 44)
  - Colleges-Michigan State-Football-Games Book 3 P-Z and Miscellaneous, 1936-1982 (Box 45)
  - Colleges-Notre Dame-Football-Games, 1938-1982 (Box 45)
  - Collins, John Norman-Murderer, 1969-1982 (Box 45)
  - Communists-Detroit-Book 1 A-Z, 1939-1954 (Box 45)
  - Communists-Detroit-Book 2 Miscellaneous, 1919-1981 (Box 45)
  - Communists-United States-Book 1 A-Z and Miscellaneous, 1919-1972 (Box 45)
  - Communists-United States-Book 2 Miscellaneous, 1948-1961 (Box 46)
  - Communists-United States-Book 3, 1938-1981 (Box 46)
  - Communists-United States-Inquiry, 1919-1967 (Box 46)
  - Communists-United States-Series, 1947-1950 (Box 46)
  - Comstock, William-Politician-Book 1 A-G, 1926-1949 (Box 46)
  - Comstock, William-Politician-Book 2 G-Z and Miscellaneous, 1924-1966 (Box 46)
  - Coughlin, Fr. Charles E.-Catholic Book 1 A-M, 1930-1979 (Box 47)
  - Coughlin, Fr. Charles E.-Catholic Book 2 N-Z and Miscellaneous, 1933-1982 (Box 47)
  - Couzens, Frank-Politician, 1921-1952 (Box 47)
  - Couzens, James-Senator-Book 1, 1915-1964 (Box 47)
  - Couzens, James-Senator-Book 2, 1919-1968 (Box 47)
  - Couzens, James-Senator-Book 3, 1916-1937 (Box 47)
  - Couzens, James-Senator-Book 5, 1920-1973 (Box 48)
  - Crime-Detroit-Inquiry-Grand Jury, 1930-1931 (Box 48)
  - Crime-Inquiry, 1950-1974 (Box 48)
  - De Gaulle, Charles-French Politician-Book 1 A-E, 1940-1970 (Box 48)
  - Democrats-Convention-National-Book 1, 1920-1960 (Box 48)
  - Democrats-Convention-National-Book 2, 1928-1936 (Box 48)
  - Democrats-Convention-National-Book 3, 1940-1952 (Box 49)
  - Democrats-Convention-National-Book 4, 1953-1960 (Box 49)
  - Democrats-Convention-National-Book 5, 1962-1972 (Box 49)
  - Democrats-Convention-National-Book 6, 1973-1978 (Box 49)
  - Democrats-Michigan-Book 1 A-C, 1919-1982 (Box 49)
  - Democrats-Michigan-Book 2 C-O, 1924-1982 (Box 50)
  - Democrats-Michigan-Book 3 P-Z and Miscellaneous, 1920-1982 (Box 50)
  - Democrats-Michigan-Book 4 Miscellaneous, 1937-1978 (Box 50)
  - Democrats-Michigan-Book 5, 1975-1982 (Box 50)
  - Dempsey, Jack-Boxer, 1920-1982 (Box 51)
  - Detroit-Election-Results-Book 1, 1917-1970 (Box 51)
  - Detroit-Election-Results-Book 2, 1947-1982 (Box 51)
  - Detroit-Finances-Book 1 1932-1933 (Box 51)
  - Detroit-Finances-Book 2 Miscellaneous, 1912-1915 (Box 51)
  - Detroit-Newspapers-News-Employees-Strikes-Book 1, 1937-1968 (Box 51)
  - Detroit-Newspapers-News -- Employees-Strikes-Book 2, 1968-1977 (Box 52)
  - Detroit-Newspapers-News-Polls-Book 1, 1944-1982 (Box 52)
  - Detroit-Newspapers-News-Polls-Book 2, 1965-1972 (Box 52)
  - Detroit-Newspapers-News-Polls-Book 3, 1973-1982 (Box 52)
  - Detroit-Newspapers-News-Rewards-Book 1, 1934-1971 (Box 52)
  - Detroit-Newspapers-News-Rewards-Book 2, 1971-1982 (Box 53)
  - Detroit Police Department Inquiry, 1930 (Box 53)
  - Detroit-Police-Graft-Inquiry-Grand Jury-Book 1, 1939-1940 (Box 53)
  - Detroit-Police-Graft-Inquiry-Grand Jury-Book 2, 1940-1941 (Box 53)
  - Detroit-Police-Graft-Inquiry-Grand Jury-Book 3, 1941-1956 (Box 53)
  - Detroit-Police-Graft-Inquiry-Grand Jury-Piggins & Bowles, 1966-1971 (Box 53)
  - Detroit-Stadium, 1930-1977 (Box 54)
  - Detroit-Society, 1957-1981 (Box 54)
  - Detroit-Schools-Finances-Book 1 A-L, 1919-1981 (Box 54)
  - Detroit-Schools-Finances-Book 2 M-Z and Miscellaneous, 1918-1981 (Box 54)
  - Detroit-Schools-Finances-Book 3 Miscellaneous, 1960-1970 (Box 54)
  - Detroit-Schools-Finances-Miscellaneous-Book 4, 1971-1981 (Box 55)
  - Detroit-Street Railways-Employees-Book 1 A-S, 1926-1970 (Box 55)
  - Detroit-Street Railways-Employees-Book 2 S-U, 1924-1964 (Box 55)
  - Detroit-Street Railways-Employees-Book 3 U-Z and Miscellaneous, 1922-1973 (Box 55)
  - Detroit-Street Railways-History-Municipal Ownership, 1899-1922 (Box 55)
  - Detroit-Suburbs-Series-Book 1, 1953-1971 (Box 56)
  - Detroit-Suburbs-Series-Book 2, 1972-1973 (Box 56)
  - Detroit-United Railway-Book 1, 1906-1921 (Box 56)
  - Detroit-United Railway-Book 2, 1910-1922 (Box 56)
  - Detroit-United Railway-Book 3, 1906-1943 (Box 56)
  - Detroit-United Railway-Book 4, 1901-1971 (Box 56)
  - Dickinson, Luren D.-Michigan Governor, 1919-1981 (Box 57)
  - Dillinger, John-Gangster, 1933-1978 (Box 57)
  - Dingwell, John D. Jr.-Politician, 1952-1982 (Box 57)
  - Dirksen, Everett M.-Politician, 1935-1973 (Box 57)
  - Edison, Thomas A.-Inventor, 1920-1981 (Box 57)
  - Edwards, George-Judge-Book 1 A-L, 1941-1974 (Box 58)
  - Edwards, George-Judge-Book 2 M-Z and Miscellaneous, 1942-1981 (Box 58)
  - Eichman, Adolf-Spy, 1960-1979 (Box 58)
  - Eisenhower, Dwight D.-President-Book 1 A, 1943-1966 (Box 58)
  - Eisenhower, Dwight D.-President-Book 2 A-B, 1942-1979 (Box 58)
  - Eisenhower, Dwight D.-President-Book 3 B, 1942-1969 (Box 59)
  - Eisenhower, Dwight D.-President-Book 4 C, 1945-1967 (Box 59)
  - Eisenhower, Dwight D.-President-Book 5 C-D, 1946-1964 (Box 59)
  - Eisenhower, Dwight D.-President-Book 6 D-F, 1943-1969 (Box 59)
  - Eisenhower, Dwight D.-President-Book 7 F-G, 1945-1963 (Box 60)
  - Eisenhower, Dwight D.-President-Book 8 G-H, 1946-1964 (Box 60)
  - Eisenhower, Dwight D.-President-Book 9 H-I, 1945-1969 (Box 60)